If saying goddamn sends me to hell,
whose hell are we talking about exactly?
A lot of comments lately saying things
like you can't say goddamn and then
praise the Lord. I've never once claimed
[music] to be a Christian. I am the
horse sweating in church for sure. Um,
but this doesn't go to church. My
religion is nature. I listen to the wind
and the trees and my gut. There are
always these people that feel the need
to tell these other people that they are
doing something wrong because they're
not doing it the way that their religion
does it. I don't tell Christians they're
going to some terrible [music] place
don't honor the same deities I do. I'm
not out there hexing people cuz they
don't follow Hecate and Lilith or
whoever. I simply let them be. It's your
life. Do it how you're going to do it.
I'm going to do mine. So, on that note,
I'm probably going to continue to say
words like goddamn. On another [music]
note, Joe is taking a very much needed
break from social media to focus on
himself, focus on his life, focus
[music] on finding some peace. Here I am
running my little yapper with words of
wisdom and knowledge that I think you
should probably listen to. Just kind of
trying to fill the silence while he is
handling his And when he comes
back, we'll get back to the Bibles and
ancient artifacts and Mexico and
Colombia and Costa Rica, solar and
construction and all the things that he
has shared and and taught us.
Until that happens, it's you and me,
baby. Anyways, I hope you have the best
goddamn Monday.